animecornerstore.com 2006-12-22

# Privacy / Security Statement

**_Site Security at the Anime Corner Store_**

_**I Want you to Feel Comfortable Placing an Order!** _

_I know that you are concerned about Internet security. So am I! That's why we have built in some of the most advanced security technologies available for an on-line shopping site. The Store portion of Robert's Anime Corner uses a server which supports advanced 128-bit SSL encryption. Here's how it works:

**SSL encryption** is active on our site in all areas where customer information is requested. You can check to see that you have entered an SSL-active area by looking on the bottom of your screen. If you see 

**an unbroken key or a closed lock ** (depending on your browser), you will know that SSL technology is in place and ready to encrypt your information. _

_You'll see a key (Netscape) or a closed lock  (AOL & Internet Explorer).   
  
You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When you are in an SSL-active area, the first letters of our website address will change from  **"http:" ** to  **"https:" ** (the 's' means 'secure'). 

When you place your order with my store online, your information is 

**transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form , ** which is then decoded when it gets to our computers here. Your personal information, including your credit card information, is safe from prying eyes. _

_**Shop with confidence! ** _

**_Your Privacy and the Use of Your Personal Information_**

**Your Privacy Matters!**   

  * _**Email Addresses**   
We collect e-mail addresses that are supplied through my optional email mailing list. We also collect e-mail addresses from online orders. 

If you have supplied us with your e-mail address, we may contact you with news of new anime products or upcoming events, or send you an on-line newsletter from time to time. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please [e-mail](mailto:remove@animecorner.com) us.

**We do not trade, rent, or sell e-mail addresses to any other parties - ever - period.  
**

_
  * _**Postal Addresses**   
We collect postal addresses from online orders. 

If you have supplied us with your postal address, we may contact you with news of new anime products or upcoming events, or mail you a catalog from time to time. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please [e-mail](mailto:remove@animecorner.com) us. 

**We do not trade, rent, or sell postal addresses to any other parties - ever - period.**

_
  * _**Telephone Numbers**   
We do not retain telephone numbers for purposes other than contacting individuals with a question or information regarding their order. 

**We do not trade, rent, or sell telephone numbers to any other parties - ever - period.**

_
  * _**Credit Card and other Payment Information**   
We do not retain credit card numbers or other payment information for purposes other than processing your secure online orders. After your order is placed, your credit card and other payment information records are securely stored in my computer system. Any hardcopy information that is printed out locally here, and is not sent along with your order (internal copies of credit card transaction receipts, for example) is thoroughly shredded before being disposed of. **Your Payment Information is safe here!** _
  * _**Aggregate Site Statistics**   
We collect, in aggregate form only, the domain names of visitors to our site, as well as statistics about site sales, traffic patterns, and other related site information. These statistics include no personally identifying information, and will be used only for marketing, sales reporting, or to improve the design of my Web site. _
  * _**Privacy Statement Updates**   
If we decide to make any changes to this Privacy Statement, I'll post those changes here so that you can be informed._

_At Robert's Anime Corner, I am committed to using customer information responsibly. You are my number one priority, so I want you to feel comfortable placing your order online. If you have any additional questions or comments regarding my secure technology or privacy policies, please [e-mail](mailto:bob@animecorner.com) me._

_**Thank you for Choosing the Anime Corner Store!** _

_**Enjoy your anime!** _
